好的，现在来使用这个同步adapter，这个过程跟之前的
Well, we're now using the sync adapter, and things are
工作差不多一样。我们想要这个应用能够
working pretty much as before. We want the app to do
很好的进行同步，同时希望能看到我们的菜单栏里旧的内容得到
this synchronization cleverly, and we'd like to get rid of
刷新。让我们把其他这些我们需要同步的活动再来
that old Refresh menu item. Let's start by cleaning up all
整理一遍。发现其实可以确定，我们并不需要
the other routines we have to sync. So we certainly
其他像FetchWeatherTask这样的东西，还有些类似在
don't need any of this other stuff like FetchWeatherTask, or all
Sunshine 服务中用过的那些东西， 同时我们将需要把manifest 文件进行
this stuff we did in Sunshine service, and we'll want to clean
一番整理。 我们再次确定，这些东西我们都用不了
up the manifest accordingly. We certainly don't need either one of
在偏好设置中，我们则需要把它设
these anymore. And in Preferences, we can just change
置成同步。这样我们就能够在任何地方使用
that to sync immediately. So now we're really using this
同步adapter。现在看看，似乎还有一点问题，这个处理似乎并不是那么
sync adapter everywhere. We have a problem though. We're not
明智。用户在使用排序之后依旧看到
being very smart. The user still has all sorts of
一个空白的列表。我们真正想要的是一个更加
places where they see an empty list. We want to
智能的同步处理。在安卓2.2之后，安卓添加了一个周期性同步的
sync more intelligently. In Android 2.2 Froyo, Android added the
功能呢。我们可以添加一个帮助方法
ability to have sync adapter's sync periodically. We can add
在同步adapter中。
a helper method to do this in our sync adapter.
问题是，这个方法并不是跟我们所期待的一样
The problem is, this method isn't as smart as
聪明，它并不能很酷的来进行
we'd like it to be, it still won't do all
重复提示，就像我们期待的那样。
that cool batching with exact repeating alarms that we'd
庆幸的是，我们们在API 第 19 版之后我们
like it to. Fortunately, we've added something that does just
终于不需要在做这样的实现了。
that, but it's not available until API level 19.
弹性时间在处理不精确的重复警告的优势就是，
Taking advantage of flexible time to do inexact repeating arms,
能够让我们在Sunshine同步adapter 中设置一些好的默认值。
let's set some nice defaults for our Sunshine sync adapter.
首先，我们添加这些常数。为了让我们的代码更
First we'll add these constants. To make things a little
清楚，我们需要增加另一个功能，
clearer in our code let's add another function
当新的账户被创造以后来让我们调用。
that we'll call when a new account is created,
然后我们将把这些重要的参数设置一下。就像
and here we'll set some important flags. Such as
configurePeriodicSync，这个我们刚好
configurePeriodicSync, the one we
创建的。SetSyncAutomatically，没有这个设置我们的
just created. SetSyncAutomatically, without which
周期同步就没法被激活。既然这个刚刚开始
our periodic sync will not be enabled. Since we're
让我们来做一个立即同步处理，然后我们
just starting off let's do an immediate sync, then
可以从strategic调用它，并且获得一个
we can call it from a strategic place and
同步账户。最后，通过添加一个initializeSyncAdapter 函数，
get sync account. Finally, we can make the interface
我们就可以想外部提供一个界面，这使得我们
to the world a little bit cleaner by
的代码变得更清楚了。 这就让账户被简单的确定是我们
adding an initializeSyncAdapter function. That's simply makes sure
刚刚建立的那个账户。现在，我们来看onCreate函数，在
that an account has been created. And now
主要活动中的这个函数，
inside of the main activity in the onCreate, we
我们可以调用这个新的函数
can just make a call to that new
这样，这个函数将确定那些输给同步adapter 的参数是
function. And it'll make sure that the parameters for
正确的。让我们打开模拟器来看看
our sync adapter are set up correctly. Lets
这些有什么影响。
see if this has any impact on our emulator.
新的版本的Sunshine在一开始就显示了所有的
The new version of Sunshine right from the start shows all of current
天气。对于同步的
weather. For a sync with a sync
adapter来说 ，它会周期性的在后台进行同步处理。
adapter to happen successfully at periodic intervals
我们必须要由一个
in the background you must: have a
ContentProvider 来标记这些同步性，并且在SyncAdapter 中激活这个
ContentProvider marked as syncable, enable automatic sync
自动同步，来完成一个初始化的立即同步
for the SyncAdapter, do an initial immediate
或者设置一个微秒的时间段。
sync, or set an interval in milliseconds.